Charming is a animation, adventure, comedy film directed by Ross Venokur.
Three fairy tale princesses find themselves engaged
to the same guy, Prince Charming.
Lenore / Lenny (voice), played by Demi Lovato.
Prince Philippe Charming (voice), played by Wilmer Valderrama.
Half-Oracle (voice), played by Sia.
Nemeny Neverwish (voice), played by Nia Vardalos.
Cinderella (voice), played by Ashley French.
Snow White (voice), played by Avril Lavigne.
Charming is a 2018 animated musical comedy film
written and directed by Ross Venokur.
Produced by Vanguard Animation, 3QU Media, Cinesite and WV Enterprises, the film features
the voices of Demi Lovato, Wilmer Valderrama, Sia, Ashley Tisdale, G.E.M.
and Avril Lavigne.
Lovato is responsible for the executive production of the soundtrack, with Sia, Fall
Out Boy frontman Patrick Stump, and Steve Aoki contributing songs.
The film had its world premiere in Spain on 20 April 2018,
and was met with generally negative reviews.
Streaming service Netflix acquired the distribution rights to the film in the
United States, and it was released on the platform on 8 January 2021.
The film explores themes of princess, fairy tale, prince.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.